Brenda Beck collection from Tamil Nadu, India
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 9: Digital surrogates of sound recordings, 2005, The digital items described below were digitized by the donor. The collection does not include corresponding physical transcripts or analog recordings.
  - Kavadi songs, 1 wav file (24.9 MB): digital; A digital copy of this file was extracted from the original carrier by AFC staff for preservation and access purposes. The file path is provided. A recording can be found on AFC 2017/050: SR29. (Digital-carrier afc2017050_cf11)
  - Two short stories, 1 wav file (215 MB): digital; A digital copy of this file was extracted from the original carrier by AFC staff for preservation and access purposes. The file path is provided. A recording can be found on AFC2017/050: SR29 (Digital-carrier afc2017050_cf11)
  - What story unsure, 1 wav file (492.2 MB): digital; 1 wav file (44.22 MB): digital; 1 wav file (54.18 MB): digital; Digital copies of this file were extracted from the original carrier by AFC staff for preservation and access purposes. The file path is provided. (Digital-carrier afc2017050_cf11)
  - Census data, 1 wav file (0.03 MB): digital; A digital copy of this file was extracted from the original carrier by AFC staff for preservation and access purposes. The file path is provided. (Digital-carrier afc2017050_cf11)
  - Ramacamy and Palani performance, 1 wav file (0.44 MB): digital; A digital copy of this file was extracted from the original carrier by AFC staff for preservation and access purposes. The file path is provided. (Digital-carrier afc2017050_cf11)
  - Ramacamy and Palani performance, 1 wav file (0.44 MB): digital; A digital copy of this file was extracted from the original carrier by AFC staff for preservation and access purposes. The file path is provided. (Digital-carrier afc2017050_cf11)
  - Ramacamy and Palani performance, 1 wav file (0.08 MB): digital; A digital copy of this file was extracted from the original carrier by AFC staff for preservation and access purposes. The file path is provided. (Digital-carrier afc2017050_cf11)
  - Diaries, 1 wav file (0.44 MB): digital; A digital copy of this file was extracted from the original carrier by AFC staff for preservation and access purposes. The file path is provided. (Digital-carrier afc2017050_cf11)
  - Published volumes, 1 wav file (898.5 MB): digital; A digital copy of this file was extracted from the original carrier by AFC staff for preservation and access purposes. The file path is provided. (Digital-carrier afc2017050_cf11)
  - Published volumes, 1 wav file (0.88 MB): digital; A digital copy of this file was extracted from the original carrier by AFC staff for preservation and access purposes. The file path is provided. (Digital-carrier afc2017050_cf11)
  - Published volumes, 1 wav file (0.95 MB): digital; A digital copy of this file was extracted from the original carrier by AFC staff for preservation and access purposes. The file path is provided. (Digital-carrier afc2017050_cf11)
  - Web Address for Download of Thesis scan, 1 wav file (0.01 MB): digital; A digital copy of this file was extracted from the original carrier by AFC staff for preservation and access purposes. The file path is provided. (Digital-carrier afc2017050_cf11)
- Oversize materials (Box 46)
  Includes maps and charts
  - Coimbatore house-to-house caste survey, 1966
    Separated from Box 17.
  - Map of Olapalayam
    Separated from Box 18.
  - Pariayar hamlet households and map, Gannapuram
Appendices: Inventories
Attached are two pdfs: Tape Inventory and Archive Index revised. The first pdf is the original tape inventory created by Brenda Beck. It contains audio content, transcripts, transfers and other notations about the recordings. The second pdf contains the inventory of all the materials, both analog and digital, that Beck donated to AFC.